I watch American exceptionalism pop off in the comments every day because I watch people who know, who know that they have barely read anything, whose degree is from TikTok, who know that they have never left a block, who know that their circle has not done any more learning than them.
Who know that they are not considered wise by anybody.
I see these individuals on the daily.
Question me.
A 44 year old woman who has had several professional careers, who is regarded and respected as a scholar, as an artist, as an intellectual, as an activist, as a truth teller.
By notable scholars, organizers, activists, and artists the like.
I have a track record of being on point.
I ain't been wrong yet about when I call something.
And yet folks will still be souped up enough to come on this phone and talk to me like we are peers.
For some reason, folks confuse me with one of these randos out here who just picked up a phone and started making videos.
You see me on this Internet because I'm doing you a free service, not because I am here with a goal of being an Internet personality.
If you are confused by an angle that I come with, know that it is because it requires you to either ask more questions or do more research.
If I don't say something, it's because it's not time to be said yet.
And at some point, I would appreciate the respect of my own judgment being sound because I have a track record of sound judgment.
See y'all tomorrow morning, 10 a.m. Eastern on YouTube, Amanda Seals TV for views from Amanda Land.
Another source of free content I provide you, the people, straight from my brain.